Okay. And now I'm going to do a control
C to stop the server from running. It's
no longer running. I'll clear that
screen with clear. Okay. It's time for
us to add some functionality. We've got
another way to prompt our LLM. We want
to do more. So at this point I want to
mention that it's important to be taking
backups as we go to be checkpointing
because at any point particularly when
you're yoloing you could mess everything
up or the agent could mess everything up
and you have to start all over again
which would be a pain. Now the right way
to do this is using git and using
features of git that allow us to commit
at various points and we will be doing
that in the future. Uh, and if you know
how to do that already, then for sure do
that. But otherwise, the the simple way
to do it, the poor person's version of
Git, is simply to to copy and paste to
duplicate the entire folder site and
keep a backup of it that way. That way
you've got a snapshot that you could
always switch back in if you need to.
So, make sure you've done that just in
case what we do next messes everything
up so you can always recall. And if you
know how to use git, then of course just
commit. Uh, and be careful of the fact
that there's like already going to be a
git repo under the web directory that
you'll need to to remove and then just
have one git repo if you if you know
that. If you don't, just take a copy.
All right, now time to ask our agent to
do more. Okay, so here we go. I'm going
to paste in here my next instruction.
That's great. Please now add the ability
to have an AI chat with a digital twin
which can answer questions about my
career. Please use open router. My open
router API key is in thev file in the
project routt. Please use the model
named. Okay. And now I just want to
bring up open router itself. This is
open router. If you go to the models
page in the main navigation, we can look
at all the different models that open
router offers. If you type free, you get
to see all the free ones. I want to look
for ones uh called GPTOSS,
which is uh OpenAI's open-source models.
There's a free version and a paid
version. The free version, you can only
use it occasionally. I'm going to pick
the paid version. It's still super
cheap, but you can choose to use either.
Um this this is the version. I need to
refresh that. And then I'm going to copy
that model name into the clipboard. Go
back to cursor. Paste that in here. Like
so. That is the name of the model. That
is all I need to do. Make the changes.
Changes.
Make sure it works.
Let me know when ready for me. That's
all. Let's set that going. Off goes our
AI agent. I will see you back here in a
few moments when the yoloing is
complete. Okay. Well, it tells me that
an AI digital twin is wired up and
ready. The site now includes digital
twin. It calls open router. It uses the
MMV file. It's given me the
instructions.
What do you think? What's your bet? Is
this going to work? Is this going to
work? Let's see. Uh, we have to be in
the web directory, which is where we
are. pwd. There we are. We do mpm
rundev.
Well, it hasn't crashed. Now, let's
bring up a browser. Here's a browser
tab. Hold on. Make that a nice size for
you. Sorry. One second. One second. I
know it's exciting.
Okay, here we go. So, after faffing
around with that, we can go to localhost
3000. And here comes a website. It It
scrolled straight down originally. I
wonder if it meant to do that to do
digital twin chat with an AI version of
Ed to explore career milestones. Look,
it's all got the same site. It is a
beautiful site, by the way, I have to
say. Uh here we go. We scroll down and
here is the digital twin section. Very
interesting. It doesn't look like a
traditional chat, but it has these
buttons and things. All right. Shall we
try chatting with the digital twin?
Okay. Let's give it a shot. Uh, hi
there.
So, I said hi there. It's slightly
janky. It like bounced around a bit, but
I said, "Hi there. Look, look at how
it's showing here. Hello. I'm the
digital twin of Ed Donna. How can I
assist you today? Perhaps with insights
on his work, blah blah blah blah blah."
Uh, what are you most proud of?
Let's see what we get. What What is this
guy Ed most proud of? Let's see. I'm
most proud of turning a vision into
tangible impact. Building Nebula from
the ground up. As the founder said, very
nice. What a nice answer. Watching
thousands of professionals find roles
that genuinely fit them. the clearest
proof that technology can serve a deeper
human focused mission. Nicely put. So,
here we have it. We have a digital twin.
It's It's interesting the way it's
showing it here. It's actually quite
nice. It's it's different. I've seen
many digital twins and they don't tend
to look this way. So, I do quite like
it, I have to say, even if it's not not
the traditional approach, but very nice.
It does seem to be working and
presumably it's calling open router.
Well, this is really showing you, I'd
say, the the the good and the rough
edges of vibe coding. This looks pretty
good, I have to say, but there's
definitely some weird stuff like the way
when it opens up, it flips down straight
to that section. I do believe some of
this navigation at the top here. Some of
it works. Career journey works nicely.
Does that portfolio? Oh, that works as
well. Digital twin. Oh, okay. At one
point, I think this wasn't working, but
it does seem to be working right now.
Uh, so so that navigation is working.
Um, but yeah, there's the another thing
that doesn't work. These buttons here. I
tried pressing that button and nothing
happened. So, there's definitely some
things here that that that are a bit
broken. And this is where you have to go
back and iterate, iterate, iterate and
improve and and see what can be done by
going backwards and forwards. And it is
a good idea to keep backups. Uh, you
should really do it using git, but make
sure you can always go back if it ever
does something that should be reversed.
And of course, the main thing to keep in
mind here is that by by genuinely vibe
coding with YOLO, we've sort of broken
all of the rules that I said at the
first first half of of today's session.
We didn't work on an agents.md. We
haven't really been checking as we go.
And that's fine for this kind of of MVP
and for experimenting and exploring. But
if we wanted to take this further, it
would now be important to take a moment
and come back through. First of all,
test everything thoroughly and fix up
things that we're not satisfied with.
Iterate on things like the prompts and
look in at the code. And for example,
now let's take a look inside web and
find out what has this actually built
and do we understand it? And so for
example, I can come in into web into
source src and come in here look inside
app and here we could look inside API
and you'll see that there is something
called root.t ts under API chat. And if
I open this up, this is where we will
see the backend code that's getting run,
which is where it is going to uh to be
able to to call open uh call open
router. Now, let's make this a little
bit bigger and push our agent over to
the side and take a look at what's
happening here. And you can see the code
that is going to make that request to
the the the LLM. And we can now look
through this and get a sense of what's
going on. And most importantly, we can
see the prompt that's being used to tell
it who I am. And we may decide, look,
this is this is quite simplistic. This
is just a very basic prompt. We really
wanted the whole LinkedIn profile with
all the information to be sent to to the
chatbot so that it could could give us
the most robust